<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FinalYearProject</string>
    <string name="reading_desc">Read the following 3 passages out loud, and listen to the delayed audio feedback, after each passage score yourself on how you think you sounded and your scores will be saved! Make sure to check out the progress page to find your old scores and your improvement over time!</string>
    <string name="daf_desc">Delayed Auditory Feedback, is a type of altered auditory feedback that consists of extending the time between speech and auditory perception. It can consist of a device that enables a user to speak into a microphone and then hear their voice in headphones a fraction of a second later</string>
    <string name="syll_count_info">Select the correct number of syllables for the word show on screen, your score out of 10 will be saved!</string>
    <string name="ton_twist_info">Select a tongue twister to listen to and to try yourself! The list of tongue twisters has been tailored to you to you, putting the tongue twisters that contain your feared sounds towards the top!</string>
    <string name="breathing_exercise_info">Diaphragmatic breathing can be used as a tool to relax articulators and reduce stress.\n\nFollow the onscreen instructions. Sit comfortably and place one hand on your chest and the other on your belly. Breathe in slowly through your nose, ensuring your belly rises more than your chest. Exhale slowly through the mouth.</string>
    <string name="progressive_muscle_relaxation_info">Progressive muscle relaxation reduces overall muscle tension and can help alleviate the physical manifestations of stuttering, like facial tics. \n\nFind a quiet and comfortable place, and focus on gradually tensing and then relaxing each muscle group. </string>
    <string name="cycle_text">%1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="flex_rate_info">Flexible rate is slowing down the production of a word, especially the first syllable.\n\nThis technique helps in allowing more time for language planning and motor execution</string>
    <string name="flex_rate_ex_info">Speak aloud the text on the screen, stretching the vowel sound in the first syllable of the word.\n\nThis will be a guided practice session with a voice to guide you through each example.</string>
</resources>